Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jerome T. Barrett Papers, 1937-2005; Record Group 2
  - Jerome T. Barrett Abritration Case Files, Record Group 2 Series 10
    - Social Security Administration Baltimore, MD and American Federation of Government Employees Local 1923, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Department of the Navy, Supervisor, Shipbuilding, Conversion, and Repair Newport News, VA and National Association of Government Employees Local R4-2, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - US Immigration and Naturalization Service South Burlington, VT and American Federation of Government Employees, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - DC Water and Sewer Authority and Coalition of Workers, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - City of Falls Church City Employee Review Board Falls Church, VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Settle/, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Social Security Administration Baltimore, MD and American Federation of Government Employees Local 1923, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Washington, DC and American Federation of Government Employees Consil 238, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Washington, DC and American Federation of Government Employees Concil 238, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Navy Expeditionary Medical Support Command Norfolk, VA nad National Association of Independent Labor Local 1, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - American Postal Workers Union Health Benefits and Pension Funds Burtonsville, MD and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 2, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - City of Falls Church MD and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Police Corporal Franc Hicks/, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Central Pension Fun of the International Union of Operation Engineers Washington, DC and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 2, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Bear Ridge Coal Company Tazewell, VA and United Mine of America Local 6633, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - East Liverpool City Hospital Pittsburg, PA and Glass, Molders, Potters, Plastic, and Allied Workers International Union Local 333, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Medicare and Medicade Services Baltimore, MD and American Federation of Government Employees Local 1923, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Associated Coal Corporation Lighfoot No. 2 Mine Charlston, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 781, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - University of the District of Columbia and AFSCME District Council 20 Local 2087, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - US Department of Commerce Patnt and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professinal Association (POPA) Grievant Ray Johnson, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Kaiser Permanente Rockville, MD and Service Employees International Union Local 105 /R. Lopez/, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - City of Falls Church VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Bristol and Rhodes Police Department/, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - City of Falls Church VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Police Officers Bristol and Rhodes/, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Colony Bay Coal and UMWA, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Colony Bay Coal Company Chapmanville, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 9177 File 1 of 2, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Colony Bay Coal Company Chapmanville, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 9177 File 2 of 2, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Association Coal Company Rocklick Operating Unit Chapmanville, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 9177, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Water and Sewer Authority Washington, DC and American Federation of Government Employees Local 872, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Bryan Food, Inc West Point, Mississippi and United Food and Comercial Workers Union Local 1991, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Carson City, NV and Carson City Fire Fighters Association Local 2251 IAF, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - CC Board of Supervisors Meeting of 3/6/01 (Excerpt) VHS Tape Carson City and Carson City Fire Fighter's Association Local 2251, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      This is part of the Carson City Fire Fighter's Association 2003 File. It is foldered by itself due to the format
    - District of Columia Department of Correctins Washington DC and Fraternal Order of Police Department of Corrections Labor Committee Local 618 File 1 of 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - District of Columia Department of Correctins Washington DC and Fraternal Order of Police Department of Corrections Labor Committee Local 618 File 2 of 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - City of Falls Church VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Tyrone Lee/, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Colony Bay Coal Company Charlston, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 9177, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers Health Plan Department and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Police Department Washington, DC and Fraternal Order of Police, MPD Labor Committee, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Associated Coal Corporation Rocklick Operatin Unit Charlston, WV and United Mine Workers of America Local 9177, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - City of Albuquerque NM and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Local 3022, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Bakery and Confectionary Workers and Industry International Health Benefits and Pension Funds and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 2, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Metropolitan Police Department Washington, DC and Fraternal Order of Police, MPD Labor Committee, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The Wackenhut Corporation Palm Beach Garden, FL and United Federation of Security Officers and its Affiliated Local 618, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Aibertson's Inc Las Vegas, NE and Teamsters Health and Welfare Trust Plan Grievances Local 537, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office Washington, DC and Patent Office Professional Association (POPA) Union, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - US Department of Commerce Patent and Trademark Office and Patent Office Professional Association /POPA/, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Brooks and Brooks Services, Inc Washington DC and Laborers International Union of North America Local 572, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Safeway Stores Inc Denver, CO and United Food and Commercial Workers International Union Local 7, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Aggregate Industries, Inc and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 639, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Communications Workers of America Washington, DC and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 2, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Unilever Ice Cream Hagerstown, MD and United Steel Workers of America Local 9386, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - James River Bus Lines Richmond, VA and Amalgamated Transit Union Local 1764, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority Atlanta, GA and Amalgated Transit Union Local 737, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Regional Transportation District Denver, CO and Amalgated Transit Union Local 1001, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Maryland-National Capitol Park And Planning Commission Riverdale, MD and Municipal and County Government Employees Organization United Food and Commercial Workers Local 1994, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Apogee Coal Company Chapmanville, WV and United Mine Workers of America, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Water and Sewer Authority Washington DC and American Federation of Government Employees Local 631, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Prince George's County Board of Education Upper Marlboro, MD and Association of Classified Employees American Federation of Statem County, and Municipal Employees local 2250, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Board of Education of Baltimore County Towson, MD and Maryland State Teachers Association, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - City of Falls Church VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /J. Sidney/, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Board of Education of Baltimore County Towson, MD and Maryland State Teachers Association, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Communication Workers of America Decatur, GA and Office Employees Local 2, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Honeywell International and Industrial and Allied Workers Local 101 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Honeywell International and Industrial and Allied Workers Local 101 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Metropolitan Police Department and Fraternal Order of Police /Grievant-A. Holden/, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - DC Metropolitan Police Department Arbitration Brief 2, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - DC Metropolitan Police Department Arbitration Brief 3, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - DC Dept. of Youth Rehabilitation Services and American Federation of Government Employees Local 383, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - City of Falls Church, VA and City Manager's Determination of Grievance /Police Officer R. Gessner/, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Board of Education of Baltimore County Upper Marlboro, MD and Maryland State Teacher Association, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Exxon Mobil Pipeline Company Houston, TX and WCEU-USW Local 407, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Ampco System Parking Denver, CO and United Mine Workers of America, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - North Las Vegas and North Las Vegas Police Association, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Cecil County Maryland and UFL Practice Elkton, Maryland, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - AHTNA Tech Serves and ITPE Central California, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Schools and Washington Teachers Union, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - DCPS and WTU, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Professional Staff Association, MD and Marland State Education Assocation, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Jerome Barrett Assistant Director of the National Center for Dispute Settlement Arbitration Community Disputes Awards, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      There are four awards located in this folder, issues 2/5/1970, 2/14/1970, 4/8/1970, and 6/11/1970.
    - Various Arbitration Panels, 1982-1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Contains BCUE+UMWA, Fed Mediator, AAA, MNB, L-MC, Ohio SERB, Indiana Division of Labor, Deptartment of Energy and OPEIU, and Social Security Administration and AFGE
    - AAA Labor Panel, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration Roster, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Wage Study Reports L-M Study Committee of DC Police and Firefighters, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Factfinding Report Collective Bargaining by Glendale Unified School District and Employee Council, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Maryland National Park Planning Commission and UFCW Local 1994, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Various Cases without Hearings, 1983-1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Folder states that "None hearing cases after 1991 are in individual case envelopes."
    - Social Security and AFGE, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Georgia Power and IBEW, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Doctors Council of DC and District of Columbia Government, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - American Postal Workers Union and Washington Newspaper Guild, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Allegheny Port Authority and ATU, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - EACC and UMWA, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - EACC and UMWA, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Sundial Prep Coal Plant and UMWA, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - AAA and Westvaco, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Mystic Energy and Candiee #2 Mine, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Wells Whartor #2, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Eastern Association Coal and Colony Bay, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Duro BDG and Machinists, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - CHC Clintwood International and UMW Local 7528, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Pine Ridge Coal, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Social Security Administration and AFGE, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - CWA and OPEIU, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Prince George County Schools, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Marta and ATV, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - US Arm Topographucal Engineering and MFFE, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - OPEIU and Letter Carriers Health Plan, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Cow Creek Coal, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - SSA and AFCE, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Squaw Creek Coal and UMWA, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Howard University Hospital, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - International Paper U. Steelworkers, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Library of Congress, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Prince George County, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Hobet Mining, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Hobet Coal, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Lightfoot Mine UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - SSA and AFGE Virginia, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Consol Coal Leverage Mine and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Volvo Truck and UAW, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Hobet Coal and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Eagle Energy and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Westmore-Land Coal and UMWA, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - APWV American Postal Workers Union and OPEIU, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - AFSCME and OPEIU, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Nay. Center Health Statistics and NTEU, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Hobet Coal and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Washington Teachers Union, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Eagle Energy and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Peabody Coal and EAC, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - WV- Indiana Coal and UMWA, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Peabody Coal and UMWA, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Hobet Mining and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Georgia Pacific, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - SSA AFGE, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Nevamar and USWA, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - District of Columbia Water + Sewer and AFGE, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Prince George County School and Maryland Teachers Association, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - OPEIU and AFL-CIO, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - District of Columbia Police FOP, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Curtis Coal, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Washington DC Schools and AFT, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Westvaco Printers, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - CWA and OPEIU, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Metro Atlanta Transit and ATU, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Con Agra and UFCW, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Clearwater Sprinklers and Steamfitter, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - OPEIU and IBT, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Kellog and IBT, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Mt States Employer Council and UMWA, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Allegheny Sheriff and AFSCME, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Regional Transit Denver and ATU, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - District of Columbia Police, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Road Sprinkler Fitter and OPEIU, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Maple Creek Mine and UMWA District 5, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Westvaco and Pressmen, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - CWA and OPEIU, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Newmont Gold Company and IUOE, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - Navy-AFGE Indian Head, Maryland, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Coal Consol and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - SSA Baltimore AFGE, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Albertson's and IBT, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - McQuay International and UE, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Bandy Town Coal and UMWA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - Prince George County School and Maryland Teacher's Association, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Coal Arbitration Charlston, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 88)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 89)
    - DC Water + Sewer and AFGE, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 90)
    - Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporatioj and NAGE, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 91)
    - City of Falls Church, VA nad City Manager's Determination of Grievance, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 92)
    - City of Falls Church, VA and David Oglesby, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 93)
    - Howard University Hospital and District of Columbia Nurses Union, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 94)
    - Wind River Resources, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 95)
    - Howard University Hospital, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 96)
    - Howard University Hospital and NUHHCE Locals 2094, 1199, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 97)
    - Patten and Trademark, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 98)
    - Patent + Trademark and POPA, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 99)
    - Heritage Nursing Home and UMWA, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 100)
    - OPEIU and IBT, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 101)
    - Defense Department Dependant Schools and Federal Education Association, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 102)
    - District of Columbia Public Schools and Teachers Union, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 103)
    - Howard University and HERE, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 104)
    - Peabody Coal and UMWA, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 105)
    - SS Administration and AFGE, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 106)
    - Doctor's Council District of Columbia, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 107)
    - Reynolds Packaging and IAM, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 108)
    - Howard University and Independent Guards, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 109)
    - Anne Arundel County Schools and Maryland Teachers Association, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 110)
    - Washington DC Schools and AFT, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 111)
    - Defense Contract and AFGE Local 2117, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 112)
    - Gerogia Pacific and USW, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 113)
    - FCC and NTEU, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 114)
    - District of Columbia Police and FOP, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 115)
    - Howard University and Metropolitan Campus Police Officers, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 116)
    - Patent + Trademark and Professional Association, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 117)
    - Center Medicare + Medicaid and AFGE, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - Healthcare EE District of Columbia, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 119)
    - DC Government and AFSCME Arbitration Files, 2012-2013 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Census Bureau Arbitration Files, 2014 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - DC Government and AFGE Arbitration Files, 2012-2013 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Appeals Management Center and AFGE #25 Arbitration Files, 2014 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - UMWA, BCOA, AAA, Heekin Panels, 2013 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - AFGE, Census Bureau, UMWA #17, New River Health Panels, 2013 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - DC Department of Health and the DC Nurses' Association Arbitration Files #1, 2012 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - DC Department of Health and the DC Nurses' Association Arbitration Files #2, 2012 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - DC Department of Health and the DC Nurses' Association Arbitration Files #3, 2012 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - DC Department of Health and the DC Nurses' Association Arbitration Files #4, 2012 (Box 315, Folder 10)